ecommerceiq.asia 2018-11-25

# Privacy Policy - ecommerceIQ - Ecommerce in Southeast Asia, Reports, Data, Insights

**aCommerce Co.Ltd**  (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates https://ecommerceIQ.asia. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users and partners of the Site.

We use Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

#####  **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”). ecommerceIQ will in no circumstance share aCommerce client information unless explicitly informed the third party in advance.

#####  **LOG DATA**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this information to tailor the Site’s content strategy to bring more value to readers.

#####  **COMMUNICATIONS**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information.

#####  **COOKIES**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

#####  **SECURITY**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#####  **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 25th and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

* * *

 **Editorial  Policy**

ecommerceIQ covers all content, both data-driven comparative data and editorial. The latter includes written articles, video and audio resources, interactive tools, infographics and images. All sources are credited.

In all instances, we strive to ensure that data is accurate and clearly presented and that editorial content is evidence-based, in other words, that it is founded on the best market research knowledge currently available.

##### ACCOUNTABILITY

It will be open in admitting mistakes and encourages a culture of learning via user feedback. Its editorial processes will be transparent.

##### DIVERSITY OF OPINION

ecommerceIQ will be objective, impartial and even-handed. Where views differ and no industry consensus can be found, it will reflect all significant strands of opinion and state the uncertainty clearly.

##### PRIVACY

ecommerceIQ views its sources privacy as paramount and, barring legal order, will not divulge any correspondence or personal information it may hold about them without their prior and explicit permission.

#####  **CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about our Content or Privacy Policy, please contact us at hello@ecommerceIQ.asia.
